<?xml version="1.0"?>
<info xmlns:xsi= "http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	  xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://apps.nextcloud.com/schema/apps/info.xsd">
	<id>geoblocker</id>
	<name>GeoBlocker</name>
	<summary>Blocks user depending on the estimated country of their IP address.</summary>
	<description><![CDATA[This is a front end to geo localization services, that allows blocking (beta), delaying (beta) and logging of login attempts from specified countries.
Login attempts from local network IP addresses are never blocked, delayed or logged.
In the current implementation the login page is normally shown to everybody independent of the country. Also login attempts with a non existing user are failing as usual independent of the country.
Wrong Nextcloud configuration (especially in container) can lead to all access seems to come from local network IP address.
Determination of the country from IP address is only as good as the chosen service.

Countries can be specified using allowlisting or blocklisting.

Currently available localization services are:
- Geoiplookup (local programm on the host)
- MaxMind GeoLite2 (local database accessed via PHP API)
- Data from Regional Internet Registries (Nextcloud SQL database build up with data downloaded from the RIRs FTP servers)

For help how to set up the localization services please have a look at the GitHub repository (homepage on the right side).]]></description>
	<version>0.5.16</version>
	<licence>agpl</licence>
	<author mail="homeitadmin@seypro.de">HomeITAdmin</author>
	<namespace>GeoBlocker</namespace>
	<category>security</category>
	<website>https://github.com/HomeITAdmin/nextcloud_geoblocker/</website>
	<bugs>https://github.com/HomeITAdmin/nextcloud_geoblocker/issues</bugs>
	<repository type="git">https://github.com/HomeITAdmin/nextcloud_geoblocker.git</repository>
	<screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/HomeITAdmin/nextcloud_geoblocker/master/img/1.PNG</screenshot>

	<dependencies>
		<nextcloud min-version="29" max-version="31" />
	</dependencies>
	
	<commands>
		<command>OCA\GeoBlocker\Command\LocalizationService\ResetDB</command>
		<command>OCA\GeoBlocker\Command\LocalizationService\UpdateDB</command>
		<command>OCA\GeoBlocker\Command\LocalizationService\ListServices</command>
		<command>OCA\GeoBlocker\Command\LocalizationService\SelectService</command>
		<command>OCA\GeoBlocker\Command\LocalizationService\ResetCountries</command>
	</commands>

	<settings>
		<admin>OCA\GeoBlocker\Settings\Admin</admin>
		<admin-section>OCA\GeoBlocker\Settings\AdminSection</admin-section>
	</settings>
	
</info>
